Go！Go！
走！走！
Yo，Jimmy，man，give me the status.
唷，吉米，伙计，告诉我情况
- Tell me we good。- We got it，man.
- 告诉我都准备好了 - 我们准备好了，伙计
Beautiful。It's gonna be an all-timer tonight.
很好 今晚有好戏看了
All right，all right，all right。Fire 'em up！
好，好，好 启动吧！
We go live in five.
我们尽情快活吧
It's time for ignition and straight automobile pimp.
是时候启动你们的车啦
Let's do it，man。Let's go.
我们来吧，伙计 走
《速度与激情2》
- Ow，girl！- Sorry！My bad！
- 哎哟，小妞！- 对不起！我的错！
All right，ladies！We're good！
准备好，姐妹们！我们是最好的！
We're good.
我们是最好的
That's it，babies.
太正点了，宝贝
Come on，Tej。Let's get this race going！
来吧，泰 快让比赛开始吧！
Whoa，whoa，man。Wait a second，man.
噢，不，伙计 等等
You cats are first wave，man。Where's your fourth at？
你们是第一个来的，伙计 你们的第四个人呢？
- Yo，it was Joaquin，but he had to work the graveyard shift。- What？
- 唷，是卧金，但他要上夜班 - 什么？
Graveyard shift，man？Yo，why don't you run with us，Tej？
上夜班？唷，为什么你不和我们比？泰
Hell，no，I'm not runnin' with y'all，man.
该死，不，我不和你们比
Either you find a fourth or you don't race.
除非你们找到第四个人，否则就比赛就取消
- How 'bout that，huh？- We should find two…
- 怎么样，哼？- 我们应该找两个…
so we don't have to roll with skirt here.
那我们就不必和那姑娘玩
[Spanish]
[西班牙语]
Oooh！Idiota.
哦！
- [Spanish] - Whoa。Whoa。Wait a second.
- [西班牙语] - 喔 喔 等等
Why don't I just find y'all a fourth and we settle this on the streets，huh？
何不让我找第四个人来比赛 然后在比赛中解决问题呢？
- Bring him on。- Anybody I want？
- 带他过拉吧 - 我找任何人都行？
- [Spanish] - No matter who it is.
- [西班牙语] - 不管是谁
Yeah.
是
Yeah。Yeah，man。You wanna race tonight？
嘿 嘿，伙计 今晚想参加比赛吗？
- Yeah。You know I could use the money。- You got four minutes.
- 是的 你知道我需要钱 - 你只有四分钟赶过来
All right。I'll be there.
好，我就到
The race starts in four minutes.
比赛四分钟后开始
All right，girls。Let's do this.
好，姐妹们 我们加油
[外语]
- You think you gonna win baby？- What you think？
- 你认为你会赢？- 你怎么认为？
- You better。We got rent to pay。- I know this.
- 你最好赢 我们还需要钱付房租 - 我知道
[Spanish]
[西班牙语]
I'll get you when you get a car worth racing.
你有好车来比赛的时候我和你比
Yeah。There's our fourth right there.
耶 我们的第四个参赛者来了
Shit。It's Brian.
妈的 是布赖恩
Yeah，Brian.！I love you，Bullet.！
耶，布赖恩！我爱你，子弹！
- What's up，Tej？- What's happenin'，dude？
- 近来怎么样，泰？- 你在忙些什么？伙计
- Thanks for the invite。- No problem at all，man。Just，uh
- 谢谢你邀请我来 - 没问题，伙计 只是，呃…
Just remember me when you wax，a'ight？
赢钱别忘了我，好不？
- They got deep pockets？- Real deep.
- 他们的口袋钱多吗？- 非常多
- What's up，Suki？- What's up，Bullet？
- 你好吗，舒琪？- 你好吗，子弹？
- What do you say we kick it a nickel？- [Spanish]
- 我们来赌一把怎么样？- [西班牙语]
Nobody said nothin' about raisin' the stakes.
没人说要加大注码啊
If that's the case，why don't you ask these nice people here…
如果那样的话，你何不问问这里的人…
- to back off the line so you can go home？- Oooh！
- 那样你就可以回家了 - 喔！
Hey。Hey。Hey.
嗨 嗨 嗨
Okay。Thirty-five large.
好 三千五
[Spanish]
[西班牙语]
Thirty-five large，huh？
三千五，哼？
Either that or you can go home，brah.
你也可以选择回家
Yeah.
好
- It's all there。- It better be.
- 全部拿去吧 - 最好
Damn，Suki。Uh，when you gonna pop my clutch，huh？
糟糕，舒琪 呃，要参加吗？哼？
As soon as you get the right set of tools.
你把东西准备好我就参加
Yeah，a'ight.
是，好的
All right，back up。Back up。Let's go。Let's go.
好，退后 退后 走 走
Whoa！
哇！
Back y'all asses up。Back up。Back up.
你们都退后 退后 退后
Before you turn into barbecue around here.
在你变烤肉之前快退后
It's not a game。This is serious.
这不是游戏 这是认真的
All right。Back up。Back up。Get off the street.
好 快退后 退后 离开街道
Let's go。Back it up。Back it up.
快走 退后 退后
Everybody keep your hands real，real clear，all right？
每个人都把眼睛放亮了吧？
'Cause I got a surprise for y'all this evening.
因为今晚我要给你们惊喜
- Go，SlapJack！Go，baby！- I got this。I got this.
- 加油，杰克！加油，宝贝！- 我一定要赢 我一定要赢
[Spanish]
[西班牙语]
Ready.
准备
Go！
开始！
Oh，hell，no！
噢，天啊，不
Aaah！
啊！
Aha！
啊哈！
You ain't passin' me，dawg。You ain't passin' me。Come on！
你超不过我，笨蛋 你超不过我 来啊！
What you got，man？
你说什么？
I told you you weren't gonna pass me.
我说你超不过我
- Move，bitch！- Ha！
- 闪开，狗娘养的！- 哈！
Pendeja.！
[西班牙语]
[Spanish] Uh uh。Not tonight，baby.
[西班牙语] 唔 唔 今晚轮不到你，宝贝
Bend over，boy.
撞你屁股，小子
Damn，girl！
妈的，小妞！
Last turn。Last turn.
最后一轮，最后一轮
Oh，too wide！
噢，太宽了！
Home stretch，baby！
冲刺直道，宝贝！
Whoo-h-h-hoo！Let it go，dawg！
喔-喔-喔！我们走，笨狗！
[Spanish]
[西班牙语]
Yes！
正！
[Spanish]
[西班牙语]
I can smell you！
哈哈，我就追上你了！
Yo，Jimmy，hit it，baby。Hit it！
唷，吉米，启动，伙计 按！
A'ight。Y'all see that？
好 你们看见了吗？
Told y'all I had a surprise.
告诉你们，我有个惊喜
How you like that for a finale？
这样的终点怎么样？
Bridge.
渡桥
- Oh！- Whoo-hoo！
- 哦！- 喔！喔！
Yeah！
耶！
Shit！
妈的！
Huh？Oh，hell，no！
哼？哦，天啊，不！
Whoo！Smack that ass！
喔！爽极了！
Yes！
耶！
Tell me y'all saw that，man。Bullet and Suki sprayed the bridge，
告诉我你们看到什么 子弹 和 舒琪 飞跃过渡桥
and I need to start making y'all pay to see this shit.
我要向你们收观赏费
I got over 10 stacks for my man right here，a'ight？
我把这10叠钱给他，对不？
That's what I'm talkin' about，man。play with it.
这就是我所说的，伙计 一起合作
- Smells good，don't it？- Yeah，I'll buy that。Right there.
- 闻起来很爽，是不？- 是，这就是我想要的 给
Right。Y'all see this？Everybody take a real good look.
对 你们都看到了吗？所有人好好瞧瞧
This what you call mutual respect。A'ight，let's clear out.
这就是所谓的相互尊敬 好，我们散场吧
Anybody down for another race？
下一场谁要赛啊？
Shit！
妈的！
Hey，uh，make sure you bring that body by the garage later，a'ight，
嗨，嗯，迟点你肯定要拿车去修了
so，you know，we can work on that front end of yours.
所以，你知道，这也许就是你们的结束了
Watch out。'Cause maybe I will.
当心点 因为我也许会回来的
Yeah.
耶
What's up，man？
怎么啦？
Hey，where you going？
嗨，你去哪里？
- It's time to get out of here。- Why's that？
- 是时候该离开这了 - 为什么？
Oh，shit！
噢，天！
Nissan Skyline。Got him.
莉萨 跟上他了
Shit！Shit！
妈的！妈的！
Shit
妈的…
Shit.
妈的
Damn！
该死的！
Let me see your hands！put 'em up！
让我看你的手！举起来！
This is him。We got him.！
就是他 我们抓到他了！
- So，how long you been in south Florida？- A while.
- 你在南佛罗里达待了多久了？- 一段时间
Before that？
之前呢？
We know you're Brian O'Conner，formerly of the L.A.p.D.
我们知道你是洛杉矶特警 布赖恩 欧康纳
- You've got the wrong guy。- Really？
- 你们抓错人的 - 真的吗？
How you doin; O'Conner？
过得怎么样欧康纳？
Let's take a walk.
我走走
Carter Verone。Born in Argentina.
卡特 维安 阿根廷出生
But he's lived most of his life in Miami.
但他大部分时间住在迈阿密
Now he owns the biggest import/ export business in the state.
现在他拥有美国最大的进出口生意
Unfortunately，the cartels have been successful getting drugs into Miami.
不幸地，他们的企业联合 成功地把毒品运入迈阿密
But they've had a hard time gettin' the cash out.
但他们现在很难把毒品换成现金
We've been surveilling him for a year，but we've never been able…
我们已经监视他一年了，但我们从未成功…
to put him and the money together.
地把他人赃并获
- We've swept his house，his warehouses - Nothing.
- 我们搜查过他的房子，他的仓库… - 不关紧要
Customs here has done a great job of getting us this far.
海关已经帮了我们很大的忙
I'm just here to help get them over the top.
我来这是帮你们最后一忙的
I was able to get an agent in undercover…
我们有一个卧底…
working travel and logistics for him.
是为他打理旅行和后勤的
Recently，Verone put her in charge of finding some new drivers.
最近，维安 要她负责找些司机
- Right。Although we can't confirm her status right now。- You think she's flipped？
- 好 虽然我们现在不能确定她的身份 - 你认为她不可靠？
She's one of mine。She's all right.
她是我的人 她没问题
She's been in with Verone nearly a year。Even lives at the compound with him now.
她和 维安 一起近一年了 甚至现在和他同居了
Look，it was the F.B.I.'s idea to bring you in here.
注意，是FBI的主意要把你送进去
I'm against it。But we need some good drivers…
我反对 但我们需要一些好的司机…
that can put this asshole and his money together.
令到他人赃俱获
You're gonna roll with Agent Dunn here.
你要和当长官合作
And if I don't？
如果我不干呢？
Well，here's a list of the laws you broke in L.A.
嗯，这是你在洛杉矶违规的清单
Obstruction of justice，aiding and abetting。You know the rap sheet.
教唆和支持，妨碍司法公正 你知道那刑事犯登记表
Now，we can make this all go away in the interest of justice，
现在，我们可以 为了司法的利益把这些都毁了
- if you're willing to play ball。- Yeah.
- 如果你合作的话 - 好
So what's the idea here？Dunn and I are supposed to be street racers？
计划是怎么样？当和我在街上赛车？
That's right.
对
So，Dunn
当…
Looks like we're gonna be partners，bro.
看来我们要成为伙伴了，兄弟
Could you tell me right quick what would be a better motor for my Skyline，
可以马上告诉我 给我什么发动机来飚车吗
a Gallo 12 or a Gallo 24？
高卢 12 还是 高卢 24？
Um… The 24.
嗯… 24
I didn't know pizza places made motors.
我还不知道做比萨的地方能生产发动机
See，man，come on。I can't do this.
瞧，伙计，别这样 我做不来
Seriously，if this is what you're gonna give me，
我是认真的，如果你们给我这样的发动机
I may as well take my chances in Chino.
这真的机会不大
We will get someone else.
我们会找其他人
No way，man.
不，伙计
The only way I'll do this is if I get to pick the driver.
唯一的方法是我选人
All right，O'Conner，who you got in mind？
好，欧康纳，你心中有哪个人选？
This dude I grew up with in Barstow.
在巴斯拖 和我一起长大的家伙
- Who's that？- Roman pearce.
- 是谁？- 罗马 皮斯
Oh！What
喔！太…
- That's your boy in the Monte Carlo？- Yeah，that's him.
- 这就是你蒙特卡洛的兄弟？- 是，就是他
Yeah，he's got some skills。Mm - hmm.
- 嗯，他有点料 - 唔 - 嗯
And he's crazy as hell，I'm telling ya.
他很疯狂，我告诉过你
In a good way though。He's the man for the job.
另一种想法 他适合这工作
He's got quite a record，including three years upstate.
他有不少案底，包括最近这三年
Says here he's on house arrest now。Can't go more than 100 yards from his home.
他现在被软禁 不能离开他家100码
Roman pearce.！
罗马 皮斯！
Whoo-hoo！
喔-呼！
He always said he'd be famous.
他总是说他出名了
pearce.！
皮斯！
Roman pearce！
罗马 皮斯！
- Yo，whatever happens next，just let it go。- I ain't in it.
- 唷，不管发生什么事，别插手 - 我不插手
Rome！
罗！
Only my homeboys call me Rome，pig！
只有我家乡的伙伴才叫我罗，猪！
- I'm not a cop anymore，bro。- Is that true？
- 我不再当警察了，兄弟 - 真的吗？
- Blondie here's not a cop anymore？- That's true。No badge.
- 你这家伙不再是警察了？- 真的 没有徽章了
Whoo！Here we go.
喔！来吧
You still fight like shit。You still fight like shit
你还是那么好战 你还是那么好战…
You better chill.
你最好认真点
- What the hell are you doin' here，O'Conner？- I'll choke you.
- 你在干什么，欧康纳？- 我会掐死你
I told you to stay away from
我告诉过你远离…
- You should've told me。- I did three years，Brian.
- 你早应该告诉我 - 我三年前就告诉你了，布赖恩
I told you it wasn't my fault.
我告诉过你那不是我的错
Why did you come here，O'Conner？
你为什么来这里，欧康纳？
I got a deal for you.
我来和你交易的
When I needed your ass，you were nowhere to be found.
当我需要你的时候，我却找不到你
Now you tryin' to hand out deals？
现在你想来施舍我？
I need you to come to Miami and drive with me.
我需要你和我去迈阿密和我开车
If you do，they'll take off that anklet and they'll clear your entire record.
如果你愿意，他们会脱下那脚镣 和清除你全部的案底
I did three years in jail.
我被监禁三年了
Three years in jail off you，Brian.
三年了，布赖恩
I know you better than you think.
我比你的想法更清楚明白
Maybe you don't。Maybe you don't.
也许你不明白 也许你不明白
You guys finished？
你们忙完了吗？
This deal legit？
这个交易合法吗？
That's right，if you do this job for us.
是的，如果你帮我们工作的话
- Told you。- Shut up，punk.
- 告诉过你 - 闭嘴，小子
So you gonna clean my record and get this thing off my ankle？
那你们会清我的案底 和帮我把这脚镣去掉？
That's right。I thought you couldn't wander more than 100 yards from your home.
对 我想你无法远离 你房子100码的地方
Why do you think I'm parked so close to the derby？
你们何不会认为 我会把车停在这铁块附近？
Man，quit playin' like you gonna pass this up.
伙计，你拒绝的话就等于放弃了
Wait。Hold up.
等等
Hey，bro，what's going on？
嗨，兄弟，怎么啦？
I don't know if I should be trusting you，man.
我不知道我是否应该信任你
Just think of it this way。It's an opportunity for a fresh start.
你这样想吧 这是重新开始的机会
- Let's just go do this。- I wouldn't need a fresh start…
- 我们来吧 - 我不需要新的开始…
- if it weren't for you。- Man，you been using that since the day you got busted.
- 如果不是因为你 - 伙计，你怎么失败的那天起就这样啊
- Now，let's just chill out and go do this。- I don't need to chill out.
- 如今，让我们冷静点干完这事 - 我不需要冷静
Yes，you do。And you need to stop blaming me for your every mistake.
不，你需要 你不要把你的过失都责备于我
And Roman pearce needs to start taking responsibility for his own actions.
罗马皮斯要开始 为自己的所作所为负责任
- You need to go to hell。- And you need to go back to Barstow.
- 你去死吧 - 你需要回去 巴斯拖
I'm not goin' back to Barstow.
我不会再回去 巴斯拖 的
Brian O'Conner，Roman pearce，meet Monica Fuentes.
布赖恩 欧康纳，罗马皮斯，这是 莫尼卡 芳特斯
- Do they have background on Verone？- They've been briefed.
- 他们有没 维安 的后台？- 他们是自己人
Good。All right，here's the deal.
太好了 嗯，情况是这样的
Verone's looking for drivers。I've arranged for both of you to join up.
维安在找司机 我安排你们两个加入
I've also hired some thugs。You know，to make it legit.
我也雇佣了一些其他人 你知道，令这真实点
- When do we start？- Right now.
- 我们什么时候开始？- 马上
What are we drivin'？
我们开什么车？
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo！
喔-喔-喔-喔！
Don't even think about takin' the convertible.
别想和我换
It might loosen your mousse.
只会浪费你的口水
No，that's cool。That's too much chrome for me anyways.
不，这驾很酷 总之我喜欢这铬合金的家伙
Damn！Where you all confiscate these rims from，man？
妈的！你们这些车哪来的？
Check in with us after you meet him.
试车后过来报道
- You gonna have any problems with these two knuckleheads？- I can handle 'em.
- 你对这两个傻瓜有意见吗？- 我能应付他们
- They give you any trouble at all，you let me know。- Thanks，Markham.
- 他们给你任何麻烦都告诉我 - 谢谢，马卡姆
I'll ride with you，cowboy.
我搭你的车，小子
- Why she gotta ride with you。- You get the convertible。Let's go.
- 为什么她坐你的车 - 你有那部车了 走吧
Turn right here.
在这转右
- So you used to be a cop？- Yeah.
- 你以前是警察？- 是
How long you been under？
你做卧底多久了？
I lost track.
我迷失了
You all right？
还好吗？
You might wanna keep your eyes on the road，playboy.
瞧着点路吧，小子
- What，you think we're gonna crash？- I haven't decided yet.
- 什么？你认为我们会撞车吗 - 我不能确定哦
What are you doin'，Brian？
你在干什么，布赖恩？
He did the 「」stare and drive「 on you，didn't he？
他在表演看着你开车，是吗？
He got that from me.
他是学我的
Once we get in here，you're on your own.
一旦我们进去，你们自己小心
Look at that one.
瞧那家伙
Hey，where did you get them cars，the bottom of a cereal box？
嗨，你们这车哪来的，食品包装盒？
Eh！Real funny，Fonzie.
呃！真好笑
Ass.
笨蛋
Roberto，Enrique，I need pictures of the drivers，
罗伯托，艾礼馗，我需要司机的照片
their license plates，their cars，and anything else you can find.
他们的许可证，他们的车，还有你能找到的任何东西
[Spanish]
[西班牙语]
Let's go.
走
Keep your mouth shut and follow my lead，all right？
把你的嘴闭上，听我的，好吗？
- I got this。- No，I'm serious now.
- 我知道 - 不，我现在是认真的
Handle your business。I'll handle mine.
你自己处理你的生意 我解决我自己的
[Spanish]
[西班牙语]
Watch your hands，brah.
小心你的手，伙计
Go in line。Let's go.
排队过来 走
Carter.
卡特
- Drivers are here。- Good.
- 司机来了 - 好
Come on.
过来
- Stay。- [Spanish]
- 在这停着 - [西班牙语]
Thank you for coming on such short notice.
谢谢你们简单听我说几句
My red Ferrari was confiscated yesterday，and it sits in an impound lot in Little Haiti.
我红色的法拉利昨天被没收了 现在放在利特尔海地
It's about 20 miles from here.
离这20英里的地方
The car isn't important。What is important is the package I left in the glove box.
车不重要 重要的是我留在车上手套箱的包
The first team back here with the package will have an opportunity to work for me.
第一队把包取回给我的人将 获得被我录用的机会
- What，we gotta audition？- Nobody's got a gun to your head.
- 什么？我们要做测试？- 没人逼你干
That's it.
就这样
Driver's licenses。pass 'em up.
驾驶证 传过来
- Before Christmas，guys。- [Spanish] Go！
- 快点，伙计 - [西班牙语] 走！
- Go！Go，man。- Come on。Go！
- 走！走，伙计 - 快 走！
Come on，cuz.
来啊，笨蛋
All right，let's see what this thing can do.
好，让我们看看这些车能多棒
Agent Markham，I've got 'em heading south on I-95.
马卡姆长官，我看到他们往南去住I-95
Yeah，I got it.
好，我知道了
They're running。What a surprise.
他们飞住了 真是惊讶
Come on。Stick with me，Rome。What you got？
快 跟我来，罗 你在搞什么？
Why must I chase the cat？
我为什么要追猫？
Smart ass.
聪明的笨蛋
Oh，yeah？You think you're the bomb，Rome？
噢，耶？你以为你是炸弹，罗？
Let's see if you still got it，Brian.
让我看看你是否还跟得上，布赖恩
All right，Rome。I got somethin' for your ass.
好，罗 我有东西要给你看
Watch this，bro.
瞧这个，兄弟
Shit.
妈的
Yeah，Rome。How do you like them apples？
耶，罗 你觉得怎么样？伙计
Show off.
你炫
That's the Brian O'Conner school of driving right there，baby.
这是 布赖恩 欧康纳 驾驶学校 宝贝
Crazy-ass white boy！
疯狂的白人！
Oh，shit！
哦，妈的！
- Hey，man。- Huh？
- 嗨，伙计 - 唔？
Get yourself on outta the street.！
在那街上别动！
Boy，that's some bad shit，man.
有糟糕事
What do we got？
查到什么？
That's good。Show me his partner.
很好 查查他的伙伴
Cars。Cars。Where are the cars？
车 车 车在哪？
Stinkin' boats。Where are the cars？
都是划船 车在哪？
I need the cars。Where are the cars at？
我要车 车在哪？
- Look in the center。Look in the center。- What？
- 瞧那中间 瞧那中间 - 什么？
- Chi-ching！Now put your blouse back on。- Hater.
- 找到了！穿上你的衣服吧 - 混蛋
Shit.！
妈的！
- Don't let 'em get away。- Not a problem.
- 别让他们逃了 - 没问题
Sit on it，Fonzie！
在那坐着吧，笨蛋！
What the hell？
什么回事？
Aw，shit！Cops.
啊，妈的！警察
- What the hell they doin' here？- Rome，no.！
- 他们在这里干什么？- 罗，不！
Time to go.
该走了
- Son of a bitch！- Juvie record for popping cars.
- 狗娘养的！- 玩车的失足青年
Two years in J.D.，then another year for aiding and abetting an armed robbery.
两年少年犯罪，一年协助和教唆持械抢劫
He's clean。Dirty but clean.
他是清白的 卑鄙，但清白的
Hm。All right.
嗯 好
Hey，man，you got somethin'to eat up in there？We hungry.
嗨，伙计，你这有吃的吗？我们饿了
Sit 'em by the pool。Mm - hmm.
- 叫他们去泳池那坐下 - 嗯 - 哼
Nice。Come on.
很好 过来
Hmm。What you checking her out for？
唔 你有没查过她是干嘛的？
I'm not checking her out.
我没查过她
- Yes，you were。- No，I wasn't.
- 不，你有 - 不，我没有
- I seen you checkin' her out，man。- Okay，I was。Now shut up.
- 我认为你在查住她 - 好，我是 现在闭嘴
- You shut up。- Don't tell me to shut up.
- 你闭嘴 - 别叫我闭嘴
Both you girlies shut up.
你们两个都闭嘴
Unbelievable.
难以置信
All right.
好
You sure are cozy in this big ol' mansion.
你确定在这大公寓住得舒服吗
Sleepin' with the enemy.
和仇人睡在一起
No，no，no。Sit down.
不，不，不 坐下
Nice Ferrari you got in the driveway.
你那驾法拉利很漂亮
I'm glad you like it.
很高兴你喜欢
Darlin'，will you hold that？
亲爱的，拿着好吗？
We did all that for a damn cigar？
我们就是为了拿雪茄？
No，you did that for a job.
不，你们是为了份工
Do you really think that I would let somebody impound my car？
你真的认为我会被人扣了车？
The boatyard's mine。Oh，by the way，
那船坞是我的 哦，顺便说说
you two owe me a gate.
你们两欠我一扇门
But I'll just take it off your cut.
但我会从你们的薪水扣的
Off our cut。Yeah.
扣薪水 好
- I like that。- Good.
- 我喜欢 - 好
What's this job you got for us anyway？
你要我们干什么工作？
Come with me.
跟我来
The house has ears in it.
屋里有窃听器
I have something I want you to carry from North Beach to the Keys.
我有些东西想你帮我从 北海滩送去基士街
- What is it？- Just put in the car what I tell you to，
- 是什么？- 你只管按我的指示把货放到车上
drive it to me and don't let anyone stop you，understand？
开过来给我，别让人拦截了，明白吗？
Yeah。Any chance of cop trouble？
是 有可能被警察找麻烦吗？
No。I'm buying you a window of time，but it's not gonna be open very long.
不会 我会替你买通警察，但时间不会太长
You make it，
如果你成功的话
and I'll personally hand you 100 G's at the finish line.
我会亲自给你们10万美金
Make it 100 G's a piece，papi.
准备好10万元吧，老板
Look，man，obviously，
瞧，伙计，很明显
- your pockets ain't nervous。- Hey，hey，hey.
- 你的口袋并不紧张 - 嗨嗨嗨
Don't ever touch me.
别碰我
Ours are empty.
我们的却是空的
Like I said，we hungry.
像我说的，我们饿了
I got an idea.
我有个主意
Why don't you two boys join us at the club a little later tonight？
你们为何不参加我们今晚的晚会？
- Yeah。pearl at midnight？- We'll get to know each other a little better.
- 耶 珀尔会来？- 我们最好相互了解一下
All right。Sounds good.
好 听起来不错
- We'll see you tonight。- See ya.
- 我们今晚见 - 今晚见
Hey，you！
嘿，你！
Your pockets aren't empty.
你的口袋并不空
- Damn。- I'll take my cutter back.
- 该死 - 把我的刀拿回来
Stupid ass.
笨蛋
Hey，man，I figured you had，like，12 or 13.
嘿，伙计，我以为你有十二三个…
You're not too bright，are you？Just get out of here.
你不太醒目，是不？快走
Same old Rome doin' the same old stupid shit.
还是以前的 罗 干着同样的蠢事
- Get off me，man。- What，runnin' your mouth？Insultin' people？
- 放开我 - 你的嘴巴怎么还这样？老损人？
Stealin' Verone's shit？
还偷 维安的东西？
Think I'm gonna let somebody stare me down？
你以为我在让人看衰我？
I didn't let nobody stare me down in jail，homeboy.
在监狱我也不会让人看衰我
Think I'm gonna let it fly on a beach？
你以为我会让他指指点点？
And you，I'll take my cutter back.
你，把我的刀还给我
His rich ass.
他这富家子
- And you're packin'！- Like you ain't？
- 那你就给脸色他看！- 你没有吗？
Exactly.
当然没有
- From here，I do the talkin'。- Looks like you wanna do a little more than that.
- 从现在开始，我来说话 - 你以为你会比我好
Oh，and what's that supposed to mean？
噢，那是什么意思？
It means you always gettin' in trouble over a female，Brian.
意思是你老因女人惹麻烦，布赖恩
Man，Tej's garage is ridiculous。He's got the best of everything.
伙计，泰 的修车场是很棒的 他任何配件都是最好的
Snap-on tools。All these lifts are brand-new。They're only maybe a couple months old.
最好的工具 全部都是新的 最久的也许也只有两个月
Hey，yo，Jimmy。What's up，man？
嗨，唷，吉米 怎么样？伙计
- What up，Bullet？- That's Rome right there.
- 你好，子弹 - 这是 罗
When you get a second，I want you to check out…
可以给我点时间吗，我想你帮我检测…
the Evo and the Spyder and make sure everything's copecetic.
那辆伊沃和斯派特，确定一切良好
Evo？Where'd you get an Evo from？
伊沃？你的伊沃哪来的？
- Well，it's a long story。- I got you，man.
- 嗯，说来话长 - 好，我明白了
- All right，thanks，Jimmy。- Come check this out.
- 好，谢谢，吉米 - 过来检测一下
It's so hot and humid out here，I can't even wear no drawers.
这又热又潮湿，我甚至不想穿衬衣了
- Yeah，tell me about it。- Look at all this potential out here.
- 嗯，有话直说吧 - 哈哈，你瞧瞧
Don't do that，man.
别这样，伙计
Damn！
该死的！
Damn。Baby.
妈的 宝贝
Girl，you know your boy can help you put that fire out.
小妞，你知道我可以让你更惹火
Look at the bubble on that
瞧那上面的泡泡…
- That's cool。- That's serious right there.
- 酷弊了 - 在这严肃点
You're making me lose money。Don't do that to me right now.
你让我输钱啦 现在别搞我
I cannot take that right Come on，Ray！Do it！
我现在赔不起啊… 加油，雷！上啊！
Hey，Tej parker，
嗨，泰帕克
Roman pearce.
罗马皮斯
- Come on，baby - Basically，he's the man to know in Miami.
- 加油，宝贝… - 基本上，他在迈阿密是个名人
He's got his finger in absolutely everything.
他什么事都搞得定
It's just the way it is.
情况就这样
- What's goin' on，Suki？- What's up，baby？
- 在干什么，舒琪？- 你好吗？宝贝
- How you doing？- I'm good。How you doing？
- 过得怎么样？- 我很好 你呢？
- What's this？What's the latest？- It's a work in progress.
- 这是什么？最近的是什么？- 只是点改进
- It's not finished yet。- That's some artistic shit.
- 还没有完成 - 就像是艺术品似的
- You got talent，girl。- Yeah，she's good。She's the best.
- 你有天赋，小妞 - 是的，她很棒 她是最好的
Do or die。Bring it home，Ray。Bring it home，Ray。Bring it home。Bring it home.
决一死战 坚持到底，雷 坚持到底，雷 坚持到底 坚持到底
Yeah，baby！pay up！pay up！pay up！
耶，宝贝！给钱！给钱！给钱！
That's how they do it out here，man？
他们什么时候来这比赛的？
- Every day。- That's crazy.
- 每天 - 真是疯狂
Right here，right now。What's up，man？You don't look too happy.
此时此刻 你好吗？伙计 你看起来不太开心啊
A'ight？Expeditiously，man。I need it quick right here。What's up？
是不是？快手点，伙计 我要快点 好吗？
Thank you。Thank you。All right。How you feeling？A'ight？
谢谢 谢谢 好 感觉怎么样？还好吗？
- A'ight。Thank you。- Thank you，man.
- 很好 - 谢谢 谢谢
- Not too bad。- Whoo！
- 不错嘛 - 喔！
I'll see you about your money，homey。You race too？
赚得不少啊，伙计 你也参赛吗？
No，man.
不，伙计
I hit a wall doin'，like，a buck 20 couple years ago，you know？
我大概二十多年前开车撞了墙？
Ever since then，I just been organizing and collecting，man.
从那时到现在，我只负责组织和收款
Tej，check it out。He's gonna be in town for a while.
泰，听着 他会在这里呆上一阵
Is there anyway he could use that cot？
他能否在你这小住一段时间？
What's wrong with your place，man？
你的地方怎么啦？
No，I don't wanna stay with him。He got bad habits.
不，我不想和他呆一起 他有坏习惯
A'ight，man。Whatever，man.
好吧 怎么都好
Show him around real quick，a'ight？I'll be up there in a minute.
带他周围走走？我很快就上去
Thanks.
谢谢
A'ight，who want a chance to win their money back？
好，谁要机会想赢回钱来的？
What's up，Jimmy？So you ever seen anything like this before？
怎么样，吉米？以前你看过这样的东西吗？
No。Both of them are wired up like I never seen before.
没有 两辆车的缠线以前我都没见过
- What？- Yeah，man。They got us wired with G.P.S.
- 什么？- 是的 他们绑定了GPS
That's why Markham knew we were gonna be at that impound lot.
所以 马卡姆 知道我要去哪
Yo，you the master mechanic。Why don't you just yank that shit up out of there？
唷，你精通机械 何不试试解了他？
I'll try，but this ain't LoJack.
我试试，但这不简单
The D.I.S。box，the engine management system，hell，the main harness
那DIS盒子，发动机管理系统 主要是放在…
The G.P.S。is spidered into all of that.
GPS 的三角架插在里面
Hey，tell me somethin'，man。Do I even want to know where the Skyline is，dawg？
嗨，说说你这车哪里来的？
Or where you been the past couple of days？
这几天你都哪去了？
- Or where the hell you got these rides from？- They're hot.
- 你这车哪里来的？- 很不错！
Yeah，they hot。They wired so hot that whoever's trackin' these things will know…
是很不错 就是因为很不错 以至于每次你们…
every time you don't wear your seat belt.
系不系安全带他们都能知道
All right，Jimmy，just do what you can do，bro.
好，吉米，你尽力吧，兄弟
- I got ya。- Thanks，man.
- 明白 - 谢谢
Man，we need to get these on the street ASAp.
我们得把这尽快推广出街
Hey，bro，check it out.
嗨，兄弟，听着
You see that Cadillac across the street over there？
你看到街那边那辆卡迪拉克了吗？
- Yeah。- Yeah，well，they've been on us since we left Verone's house.
- 是的 - 嗯他们好像自从我们离开 维安后就一直在监视我们
[Spanish]
[西班牙语]
Hey，man，I'll clean your windshield for you.
嗨，我帮你清洗挡风玻璃
What are you doin'，man？
你在干什么
[Spanish]
[西班牙语]
Everything's copecetic，homey。[Spanish]
我全部都知道啦，笨蛋 [西班牙语]
Kiss my ass，putos.
见鬼去吧，笨蛋
Shit！
妈的！
Let's go！Let's go！Let's go！
走！走！走！
[Spanish]
[西班牙语]
He's gonna blow our cover before we even get started.
他想在我们开始之前就起我们底
- Hey，Bilkins，can you tell me what went wrong？- That's what I wanna know.
- 嗨，比尔金斯，告诉我有什么不妥？- 我也想知道有什么不妥
Show me your hands！Come on。Keep 'em up！
举起手！快 双手举起！
- What's this about，man？- Hey，w-what's goin' on？
- 这是什么回事？- 嗨，怎么啦？
Hold this。You think you can shoot at me？I'm a goddamn federal agent！
听着 你以为你可以射我？我是联邦成员！
What are you talkin' about？Get your damn hands off me！Get him away from me！
你在说什么？把你的手拿开！把你的手拿开！
Just 'cause you wear a badge don't mean you can come in and mess shit up.！
别以为你穿着警服 就可以进来搅和！
- Get your hands off of me！- You're lucky I didn't shoot you.
- 把你的手拿开！- 你应该庆幸我没射到你
- Shut up，Rome！- Don't tell me to shut up，Brian！
- 闭嘴，罗！- 别叫我闭嘴，布赖恩！
You almost blew our cover，old man.
你差点让我们暴露了
You shouldn't have shown up like you did.
你不该在那里出现
What，you didn't know Verone was testing us？
什么，你不知道维安在试我们？
- No。I thought you punks were running。- Running！
- 是的 我以为你们在逃跑 - 逃跑！
That's great。That's real great！
那好 那真是太好了！
Oh，and if Rome wanted to shoot you，you wouldn't be here right now.
噢，如果 罗 要射你，你现在不会站在这里了
All right。We gotta get this under control.
好 我们要控制这局面
Hey，that's mine.！
嘿，那是我的！
- So？- So tell me what you know.
- 那又怎么样？- 告诉我你所知道的
Well，Rome and I will be making a run for Verone.
罗和我会帮维安送货
I'm not sure when and where。But he did say he bought us a window.
我不确定时间地点 但他说了他给我们买通了关卡
I'm assuming from the local cops.
我觉的肯定是和当地警察串通
I can talk to some of the guys at the local p.D.
我可以跟当地的一些警察谈谈
No。No good。If Verone's got some of them on the payroll，
不 这样不好 如果 维安 买通了他们
then we can't let them know our operation.
我们不能让他们知道我们的计划
Exactly。In addition，
正是 另外
Verone told us that he himself would be waiting at the drop.
维安 告诉我们说他会亲自在终点等我们
That's good news。If you're gonna be delivering drug money to him，
这是好消息 如果你们是把毒品的钱带给他
- then we can get him for laundering。- No，there's only one problem.
- 那我们就可以逮捕他 - 不，有个问题
- What's that？- Fuentes Verone's tappin' her.
- 什么问题？- 芳特斯…维安在拉拢她
- Tappin' her？Tappin' her how？- That is crap！
- 拉拢她？如何拉拢她？- 胡扯！
What you talkin' about，homeboy？We know what we seen.
你在说什么？伙计，我们知道我们看到什么
What do you think，O'Conner？You think she's compromised？
你怎么认为，欧康纳？你认为她在妥协？
- You should know。- What's that supposed to mean？
- 你应该知道 - 什么意思？
What？You mean your old pal O'Conner didn't tell ya？
什么？你的兄弟欧康纳 没告诉你？
He flipped on Bilkins in L.A。Gave his mark his car keys and let him disappear.
他在洛杉矶的时候背叛了比尔金斯 把车钥匙给了马库斯让他走了
That's why he's not a cop anymore.
所以他现在不再是警察
So what do you think，expert？
那你怎么想？专家
Man，I don't know.
我不知道
All right。We'll keep an eye on her.
好 我们会留意她的
We're out of here.
我们走了
- You let your man go，huh？- Drop it。I don't wanna talk about it.
- 你放你的兄弟走了，哼？- 别提了 我不想说这个
Drop it，hell！I wanna hear about this，homey.
不提？，妈的，我想知道这事
I said forget about it，cuz.
我说，忘记它 笨蛋
We got Fuentes in with Verone，Markham tryin' to blow our cover…
我们知道 芳特斯 和 维安相处得很好，马卡姆 试图揭我们的底…
and we got two wired cars that are no better than that damn ankle bracelet of mine.
而我们两辆车有监视，真他妈的不比我的那个脚镣差
I'm-a tell you，brah。You let your man Markham do that shit again in front of Verone，
我告诉你，兄弟 如果 马卡姆 再在 维安 面前乱来
- that's gonna be our ass。- I know，man。I know.
- 那将是我们的死期 - 我知道，我知道
It's gettin' thick real quick，and we may need a way out.
我在尽快想办法，我们需要个摆脱困境的办法
- We gotta come up with some exit strategy。- Exit strategy，huh？
- 我们要想点脱身之计 - 脱身之计？
Yeah.
是的
I like the way that sounds。What you got in mind？
我喜欢这个方法 你怎么想的？
I don't know，man。But we need two more cars.
我不知道 但我们需另外两辆车
Yeah。Here they come.
耶 他们来了
Fonzie and Fabio。Glad you can join us.
芳兹和伐利奥 真高兴你加入
We heard you boys wanted to get rid of those CrackerJack toys.
我们听说你们想开那些好东西
No。Actually we just figured those cars you got deserved better drivers，
不 我只是觉得你们的车 要有更好的司机
which is why we're gonna take 'em off your hands.
所以我们要从你们手里夺过来
- You know，why don't we settle this now？- Wait，wait.
- 何不现在就来呢？- 等，等等
How about we settle this on the blacktop，huh？
我们和不在路上解决？
Each car does it down and back，tag-team style
每辆车一个来回，接力方式…
- for slips。- Loser walks home.
- 输了怎么样 - 输的走路回家
- We came to race。- Well，load 'em up then.
- 我们比过吧 - 好，准备好吧
Come on，bro。Let's get these cars.
加油，兄弟 赢到这两辆车来吧
All right，check it out。There's no way we gonna beat these guys straight up.
好，听我说 如果硬碰硬的话 我们没办法赢这帮家伙
The Hemi's puttin' out about 425…
他们的车最高时速能达到425英里…
and that Yenko will snap a speed on about five seconds flat.
另外一辆车5秒就能飙到最高速
We're gonna have to pull somethin' out of our ass.
我们必须想点办法
The only thing I can think of is save the spray for the way back，the return trip.
我想到的唯一的方法就是在回程是加油
- Done deal。- All right。Let's do this，bro.
- 好 - 好 加油，兄弟
I'm gettin' that orange one.
我搞定橙色这辆
You ain't ready，Fabio！
准备好了吗！
All right。You each got a barrel to go around down at the end of the road.
好 你们开到街尾的油桶转个圈回来
The second wave gotta sit tight till your partner crosses this line right here.
第二个上的 要等你的伙伴越过这条线以后
First team to go down and back twice wins the race.
第一个来回两次的算赢
At which point，
重点是
the losers will hand over them keys.
输的要把他们的钥匙交处理
Otherwise，you'll be eatin' breakfast through straws from now on.
不然从今天开始 你们就要用吸管吃早饭了
Comprende？
明白吗？
I get it.
知道了
Oh，this means you too.
噢，你也一样
- I got it。- A'ight.
- 我明白 - 好
Let's race.
那我们开始吧
Come on，baby.！You got this，Rome。Let's do it.
加油，宝贝！你行的，罗 加油
Hey，you gone，homey。I got this。This is done.
嗨，你快走吧，伙计 我赢定了
You about to lose your car.
你输定你的车了
- Do it，Rome！- Come on。You got it.
- 加油，罗！- 加油 你赢定了
You think I'm worried about this fool，man？
你以为我会担心这小子吗？
This is nothin'.
这不值一题
- Aw，no。- American muscle.
- 啊，不 - 美国肌肉
Your engine ain't as big as your mouth.
你的引擎 不知道有没有你的嘴那么厉害
Gotta smoke 'em。Gotta smoke 'em。Gotta smoke 'em.
搞定他们 搞定他们 搞定他们
- All right，here we go。- It's all right，baby。I'm gonna handle this.
- 好，我们开始吧 - 好，宝贝 让我来吧
Handle it.
你来
Ready and… go！
预备… 开始！
You ain't ready。I run these streets.
你还没够料 我才是这条街的老大
Woo-hoo！
喔-噢！
Romey Rome。You ain't heard of me？
你没听见吗？
Oh，shit.
噢，妈的
Oh，yeah！
哦，耶！
I'm-a get you。Oh，I'm-a get you！
我一定追到你 哦，我一定追到你！
Where's your big mouth now，boy？
你个大嘴哪去了，伙计？
That car's going home with me，homey.
你的车跟我回家
Oh，shit。Eat this，sucker！
噢，妈的 试试这个，小子！
Shit！
妈的！
Yeah，boy！Go，Korpi！
耶，伙计！上！
Sorry，blondie。How does that dust taste？
对不起，伙计 后尾尘味道怎么样？
I don't know.
我不知道
Come on，Rome.
快点，罗
What the Good move，kid。Let's see if you got the balls。Come on！
天啊…好身手，小子 瞧瞧你有没有胆量 来啊！
Whoo！
喔
Goddamn！Come on！
妈的！快！
Come on，Brian。Bring it home，man.
加油，布赖恩 赢回家
Got two new cars！That's all my man！
赢了两辆新车！都是我的啦！
Damn！
该死的
Y'all ain't ready，homeboy。Get to walkin'，Fabio.
你们还没够格 走回去吧
Use them bus tokens，partner.！
做巴士去吧，伙计！
Hey，how you doin'？
嗨，你好吗？
- Good。What you need？- We're guests of Mr。Verone's.
- 很好 能帮你什么吗？- 我们是 维安 的客人
- It's a 「」hoasis「 in here，brah。- Yeah.
- 好多美女啊 - 是
- Lots of potential。- Damn。You got a pen？
- 机会大把啊 - 该死的 你有笔吗？
Phew。It's about to get serious，brah.
我都快忍不住了
Look at that girl on the swing right there.
瞧那个在那旋转的女孩
Hey。You guys did something right.
嘿 你们干得很好
- Verone never socializes with hired help。- Then what's that make you？
- 维安 从不邀请工人参加这样的活动 - 那你怎么会在这？
- Where's he at？- He's on his way.
- 他在哪？- 他在路上
- You and Verone don't go everywhere together？- What's that supposed to mean？
- 你和 维安 不是形影不离的吗？- 你这是什么意思？
Nothin'.
没什么
Huh。I'm-a go take a piss.
哈 我去小个便
You go do that.
你去吧
- What is his deal？- He doesn't trust people that carry badges.
- 他到底怎么啦？- 他不相信警察的
So you talk like you know.
你在说你的事吧
Yeah。I'd been a cop about two months…
是 我当过两个月的警察…
when Roman was busted in a garage raid.
罗在一次车库搜查中被抓
He had eight sets of wheels in his possession，each and every one of them hot.
被查出有8个来历不明的轮胎
- So you busted him？- No。I didn't even know what was goin' down.
- 所以你揭露了他？- 不 我根本不知道发生什么事
But，uh，that doesn't really matter to him.
但确实和他有关
Basically，once I became a cop，
事实上，一旦我成了警察
Roman started seeing me as a friend that became the enemy.
罗就把我从朋友当成敌人了
You have a little
你有点…
Is there anything I can get for you，Mr。Verone？
有什么我可以帮忙吗？维安先生
Just tell 'em to comejoin me.
叫他们过拉见我
Oh，yeah。I was admiring this.
噢，是的 我很欣赏
Yeah，I was looking at it earlier.
嗯，我早些时候也在找
- Damn。- I wasn't about to give it to you.
- 该死的 - 我不打算给你
- What's up？- He's here，man.
- 怎么啦？- 他来了
- Where's he at？- He's over there。Don't look.
- 他在哪？- 他在那边 别往那边看
Excuse me。Mr。Verone would like for you to join him.
对不起，维安先生邀请你们过去
Let's do it.
走吧
See what I'm talkin' about？
知道我在说什么吗？
It's all right。Let 'em in.
没事 让他们进来
Go sit down。I'll talk to you in a second.
坐吧 我马上和你谈谈
- How ya doin'？- Good。You enjoying your night？
- 你好吗？- 很好 今晚尽兴吗？
- Yeah。I'm havin' a good time。- Good，good.
- 嗯 今晚玩得很开心 - 嗯，好
She's beautiful，isn't she？
她很美，是吗？
- Hmm？- Yeah.
- 哼？- 是的
She's gorgeous.
她很美
You got balls，kid.
你很有胆量，小子
I can appreciate that.
我很欣赏
Women are a very powerful force.
女人有很强的力量
You see the blond sitting with the gentleman right here？
你看到那边和一位先生 坐在一起的金发女郎了吗？
Five minutes of her time，and she can get anything she wants from him.
她只需只需5分钟，就能从他身上得到她想要的
- I love your hair。- Watch.
- 我喜欢你的头发 - 瞧
I wonder where they're going。Sit down.
不知道他们会去哪里 坐吧
So，you，uh，lit my man's car on fire。Is that right？
你们两个家伙，令我手下的车起火了，是吗？
Yeah。I did.
是的 我干的
You see，I got a problem with authority.
你瞧，我不喜欢被管制的
Hmm。I have that same problem.
嗯，我也有同样的问题
For me，it's cops in particular.
而我，是警察在捣乱
- Let's take a walk。Come on。- We just got here.
- 我们走走吧 来 - 我们不是要来这吗
Now we're leaving.
我们现在要走了
Let's go.
走
Hey。Come on.
嗨 走
What's all that？
这是什么回事？
We're gonna have a little fun.
我们来点小乐子
- Hmm。- Thank you.
- 嗯 - 谢谢
Let's just stay a little longer.
我们再待一会嘛
Hey，Carter.
嗨，卡特
Meet，uh，Detective Whitworth.
嗯，这是怀特五兹探长
One of Miami's finest。Thank you，sweetheart.
迈阿密的一个警察 谢谢，甜心
- Are you enjoying yourself，Detective？- Yeah。I was.
- 玩得开心吗，探长？- 是的 我很开心
I mean，you know me.
我意思是，你了解我
Yeah，I do know you.
是，我确实了解你
- You been on my payroll a long time。- Verone，that ain't right.
- 你花我的钱很久了 - 维安，这可不对
Shut up.
闭嘴
I got one last job for you，Detective。You hear me？
我给你最好一件任务，探长 听到吗？
- Look，we've been all through this。- Yeah？
- 我们已经谈过了 - 是吗？
Yeah。I said I can't do it.
是的 我说过我干不了
Hmm。That's the wrong answer。The table.
唔 错了 上桌
I'm a detective，Verone！You do anything to me，
我是探长，维安！你对我干任何事
the whole force is gonna be on your ass in a minute.
警察马上就会找上你的麻烦
Shut your mouth！You fat piece of shit.
闭上你的嘴！你这只肥猪
You can stop right now.
快停手
- What the hell What the hell is that？- Sit down.
- 那是…那是什么鬼东西？- 坐下
You're gonna regret this。Just stop right now！
你会后悔的 快住手！
Once the bucket gets hot enough，Detective，
探长，一旦铁桶够热
the rat is gonna want out.
老鼠就会想爬出来
Get
拿开…
And the only direction it can go is south.
只有一个方向可以去 你的身体
Hey！Get Hey！
嗨！拿开…嗨！
Hold that.
扶住
- Get it off me！I'll forget it ever happened。- Shut up.
- 拿开！我不会追究的 - 闭嘴
Did you know that your average rat…
你知不知道一只普通的老鼠…
can chew through a steel drain pipe？
能啃破钢质的水管？
You see，you have nothing to worry about when he's screaming，Detective.
你不必担心它尖叫的，探长
It's when he goes quiet that he goes to work.
他啃的时候它就会安静下来的
Stop it.！Stop it.！Stop it.！
停！停！停！
Don't be stupid。Stop it now.
别那么愚蠢 快停手
You're in charge of the units that are watching my properties，huh？
你负责的警队看管我的货，哼？
What I want is，I want a 15-minute window…
我需要的是，15分钟的空闲…
where everybody and I mean everybody disappears.
全部人…我要全部的人…消失
- You hear me？- I can't do it！
- 你听见吗？- 我办不到！
- Stop it。I can't do it。Help.！- Okay。Monica，come here.
- 停 我办不到 救命啊！- 好 莫尼卡，过来
- Help.！Help.！- Shut him up。Shut him up.
- 救命啊！救命啊！- 把他嘴闭上
Help！Help！
救命啊！救命啊！
Help.！
救命啊！
Help！Help！
救命啊！救命啊！
He's biting me！
他在咬我
- Help.！Help.！- What？
- 救命啊！救命啊！- 怎么样？
You got somethin' you wanna say？
你想说什么？
He bit me！
他在咬我
- Yes，I'll do it.！- Do what？Say it.
- 好，我干！- 干什么？说
I'll do it。I'll give you your window.
我干 我给你空闲时间
Just get it off me！
快把它拿开！
Get it off.
拿开
You betray me，
你出卖我
and my rat here…
我的老鼠…
is gonna visit your wife，Lynn yeah
就会拜访你的妻子，林恩… 唔…
your son，Clay，and your daughter，Lexi.
你的儿子，莱克，还有你的女儿，莱西
Do you hear me？You understand me？Huh？
听到吗？你明白我在说什么吗？哼？
- You hear me？- Yes.
- 你听到吗？- 是的
I'll burn your… eyes out！I'll burn 'em out！
我把你的眼睛烤出来！把你的眼睛烤出来
Get it off me.
快拿开
- Good。Now you can go。- Get it off me.
- 好 现在你可以走了 - 快拿走
- Get rid ofhim。Let's go。- Get if off.
- 把那老鼠拿开 我们走 - 快拿开
Mm。You boys enjoy the show？
嗯 你们喜欢这表演吗？
Fifteen minutes，and then every cop in Florida is gonna be on you.
15分钟，佛罗里达 全部的警察都拿你们没办法
Be at Versailles Cafe，6：00 a.m.，day after tomorrow，ready to drive.
后天早上6点在凡尔赛咖啡厅，准备好行动
- You understand？- Yeah.
- 明白吗？- 是
Don't play games with me，or you'll be next。All right？
别和我耍花样，否则你们就是这样的下场，明白吗？
Help yourself to a little champagne。Let's go.
自便和点香槟吧 我们走
That was a damn rat，man.
这真是个该死的老鼠，伙计
Hey.
嗨
You ever… touch another man again，and I'll kill you.
你再碰其他的男人，我就杀了你
You hear me？Look at me.
听到吗？看着我
You hear me？
听见吗？
She was into it，man。What's that about？
她和他是一伙的，伙计 这是怎么回事？
And you seen the way she grabbed the dude's head.
你也看到她掐住那家伙的头
She had to，man。He was testing her。You gotta remember，
她逼不得已的 他在试她 你要记得
her ass is on the line，just like ours.
她也处于危险之中，就像我们一样
You feelin' this girl way too much.
你太沉迷于这女人了
She just like that crazy-ass trailer-raff from back-in-the-day，Tonya.
她跟当年那个疯人托雅差不多
Tonya？Man，you went out with her after I did.
托雅？你不也跟着我追求她
I mean，I couldn't let her go to waste.
我不能浪费她啊
I got you，I got you，I got you.
我赢你了 我赢你了 我赢你了
- Is that right？- See，we can race for cash，
- 是吗？- 看，我们能靠赛车挣钱
but when I step on the gas，my nitrous go blast，leave your ass in the past.
但当我踩油门的时候，我好运到来了，你只好乖乖服输
- And，Tej，you about to lose your garage。- Whatever，man.
- 泰，你快输掉你的车间了 - 管他呢
I'm a low-budget mechanic，but I overcharge.
我只是个穷机械工，但我却超支
Pay me！Let's go，man！
给钱！快，伙计！
Pay me my money。I told you，man.
快给我钱 我告诉过你，伙计
You a happy man。I'm so glad.
你是个开心的家伙 我很开心
This is my garage，boy。Royal flush！
这是我的车库 同花大顺！
- Give me this，man。- Holler，huh！Yes！
- 给我 - 噢，哼！正！
- Did I talk to him？Talk to him。- Damn.
- 我有警告过他吗？说过 - 该死的
You can't play a player。put that money back on the table。You know it's my next hand.
你不能参进来 把钱放台上 你知道我的下一手牌呢
Jimmy，how you gonna pay me back if you keep losing to Tej？
吉米，如果你一直这样输给泰 你怎么还我钱？
How ya doin'，bro？I'm gonna crash，Tej.
你好吗，兄弟 我就快破产了，泰
- I'll catch you tomorrow。- A'ight，boy.
- 我明天找你 - 好
- What are you doin' here？- Brian，they're gonna kill you.
- 你在这干什么？- 布赖恩，他们要杀了你
I heard him telling Enrique and Roberto.
我听到他下令艾礼馗和罗伯托
Once you finish the run，they're putting a bullet in your head.
一旦你完成任务，他们就杀了你
- You sure you heard 'em right？- I'm sure。I'm sure.
- 你确定你没听错？- 我肯定 我肯定
Verone's boys is outs
维安 的马子在外面…
Oh，I see what they lookin'for your little girlfriend here.
哦，我知道他们在找什么… 你的女朋友
- They don't know I'm here。I snuck out。- What are they doin' here then？
- 他们不知道我在这 我偷遛出来的 - 那他们来这干什么？
- I don't know。Maybe they're guessing。- Hey，go stall them.
- 我不知道 也许他们猜的 - 嗨，去拖住他们
- Go stall them for two minutes。- Check her，homey。Check her.
- 去拖住他们一会 - 小心她，小心她
Find what you was lookin' for？
你们在找什么？
Hey，buddy。Hi，guys。How ya doin'？
嗨，伙伴 嘿，伙计 你在这干什么？
Oh，man，y'all still mad about y'all car？
哦，你还在计较我烧你的车？
Don't even trip，homey。Come on，man。You can't take a joke？
别那么认真 伙计 开个玩笑都不行？
Brian，this isn't about being a good cop anymore or-or doing your job.
布赖恩，别管这是做个好警察 或者是干你的工作
They're gonna kill you。You guys gotta pull out.
他们要杀了你 你们要脱身了
Verone pay y'all to keep a straight face like that？
维安 难道花钱叫你们成天紧绷着脸吗？
'Cause if I was makin'money，shit，I'd get that mole removed off my damn nose.
如果我赚得到钱的话，首先就把那颗痣从鼻子上除掉
- Okay？Okay。- Yeah.
- 好吗？好吗 - 是的
How much he pay y'all anyway？
他到底给你们多少钱？
Every time I see y'all，man，y'all got the silk shirts on，
每次看见你们，你们都是穿丝质衬衫
jewelry，you know，lookin'real Miami.
珠宝，你瞧，整个迈阿密风格
You know？I caught you walkin' up in the club，
你知道吗？我看见你们走进俱乐部的时候
you got the hamburger meat all hangin' out，you know？
你们的大肥肉看得清清楚楚，知道吗？
Don't make that run，Brian。Don't make that run.
别替他们送货，布赖恩 别替他们送货
Be careful.
小心
[Spanish]
[西班牙语]
- [Spanish] - You ain't comin' on my
- [西班牙语] - 你不可以上我的…
[Spanish]
[西班牙语]
- Hey，hey！Where you goin'？- You stay right here with us，buddy.
- 嗨，嗨！你要去哪？- 你给我待在这，伙计
Don't even think about it.
想也别想
- [Spanish] - Stay your ass off my homeboy's boat.
- [西班牙语] - 快滚开我朋友的船
put the gun down！put the gun down now！
把枪放下！把枪放下！马上！
You first，asshole！You first！
你先，笨蛋！你先
I'll shoot the shit outta him！put the gun down！
我会杀了他！把枪放下！
[Spanish]
[西班牙语]
- put down the gun now！- [Spanish]
- 把枪放下！- [西班牙语]
- [Spanish] - put down the gun！
- [西班牙语] - 把枪放下！
Enough.
够了
- Enough。Shut up。- [Spanish]
- 够了 闭嘴 - [西班牙语]
Shut up。It's over。Come on.
闭嘴 结束了 过来
It's over。Let's go.
结束了 我们走
Let's have the gun。Come on。Let's go。Let's go.
拿上枪 来 我们走 我们走 走
I'm glad to see you boys are getting along so well.
真高兴你们两个家伙相处得那么好
Because tomorrow，Roberto and Enrique…
因为明天，罗伯托和艾礼馗…
are gonna be riding along with you…
会和你们一起上路…
just so that we don't have any problems.
只是为了没有任何麻烦
I'll see you guys in a bit.
我们迟点见
What the hell was she doin' in there，man？
她来这搞什么鬼？
Where'd you go this morning？
你早上去哪了？
I went to breakfast with some friends.
我和朋友去吃早晨
With friends.
和朋友？
I do have friends，Carter.
我也有朋友，卡特
Okay。I'll see you later.
好 我迟点找你
- Nice shirt，Bilkins。- It's my day off.
- 好衬衣，比尔金斯 - 今天我放假
Yeah。Well，anyhow，this is the deal.
好 嗯，无论如何，事情是这样的
Last night，Verone threatened a cop into giving us a window.
昨晚，维安 威胁一个警察 给我们一段“方便”时间
We're driving to an airstrip，in the Keys，off of Nallwood Avenue.
我们将开车到飞机跑道，通过诺木大街外的基士大街
Verone has a plane there，and he's taking off for good.
维安 在那准备好了飞机 就在那准备好起飞
- Wait a minute。How do you know this？- Monica.
- 等等 你怎么知道的？- 莫尼卡
She's doin' her job。She warned us.
她做她的工作 她警告我们
- She warned you about what？- Verone plans to kill us after we give him the money.
- 她警告你们什么？- 维安 计划我们给了他钱以后杀了我们
Driving into an ambush was never part of the deal.
自投罗网不是交易的部分
- I'm calling this off。- Like hell you are。This is a Customs case，Bilkins.
- 我决定取消行动！- 绝对不行！这是海关的行动！比尔金斯
No one's calling this off unless I do.
没有人可以停止行动，除了我
Look。This is real simple.
听着！这很简单
You make the run。You get Verone and his cash together…
你们去开车，把钱给他…
so I can move in for the bust.
我们就能抓人
All right？You don't，I will find enough charges on both of you to make you disappear.
好不好？如果你们不干的话，我会给 你们安上足够的罪名让你们永远消失
Take these。We're gonna have G.p.S。on you the whole time…
拿着 我们得用GPS随时监视你们…
to make sure you don't get any cute ideas.
确定你们不耍花样
- And to make sure nothing happens to them，right？- Yeah，right.
- 同时确保他们不会出事，对吗？- 是
- The guy's a dick，man。- Yep.
- 真是个杂种 - 是
Let me get this right.
让我这么说吧
If we don't do this，then we go to jail.
如果我们不干的话，我们就得坐牢
But if we do it，then Verone's gonna kill us.
可是如果我们干的话，维安'就会干掉我们
It's a hell of a deal，huh？
真是个他妈的交易啊，哼？
Yeah。Maybe it is.
是 也许真的很难搞
But I know this guy's got an ass full of loot…
但我知道他很有钱…
that he's ready to dump in our cars.
想都放到我们车上
And I can think of two reasons why Verone doesn't need that money anymore.
我想到两个原因 为什么 维安 不再需要钱
- Ah，here we go。- You and me.
- 啊，我们行动吧 - 你和我
Just like the old days。What do you think？
就像以前那样 你怎么想？
I think they messed with the wrong two guys。That's what I think.
我认为他们找错人了 我是这样想的
- Yo，Tej。What's up，bro？- What up？
- 唷，泰 你好吗？兄弟 - 怎么啦？
Hey，man，how quickly can you organize？
嗨，你能多快组织起来？
Look，folk，if y'all really wanna carry out this plan，
听着，伙计，如果你真的要执行这计划
it's definitely the best place to do it.
明确了最好的地点
- What do y'all think，man？- I think it's perfect。What do they store here？
- 你们怎么认为？- 我认为很好 他们在这储藏什么？
Hey，man，this thing's clean.
搞定
Slank that fitted on Came to get it on Hey，Jimmy.
嗨，吉米
- Yeah。What up？- We have any half-empty bottles of nitrous laying around？
- 是 怎么啦？- 我们还有没有半满瓶的氮气？
Sure，but I already loaded you for spray.
当然，但我已经载入在你的车子了
No。I'm thinkin' we may need it for somethin' else，
不 我要用来干其他的
'cause our cars may get a little crowded，you know？
因为我们的车可能会有点挤，知道吗？
Man，when you start eatin' so much？
什么时候你开始吃这么多？
I was in jail，brah.
我坐过牢
I know how shitty the grub is on the inside.
我知道里面的食物是多么地差
With the way things is shapin' up out here right now，
照现在事情发展的趋势
it'll be a matter of time before I'm back in there or dead.
我要么就进监狱，要么就死
So I'm tryin' to eat all I can while I can.
所以我能吃的时候就尽量吃
plus the doctor tell me I got a high metabolism.
再加上医生告诉我，我新陈代谢很快
Man，you remember us growing up？
你记得我们是一起长大的吗？
You know，playing football in the dirt.
一起在沙地上踢足球
You know，gettin' in trouble，all the stupid things we did.
一起惹麻烦，经历一切愚蠢的事情
When you got busted，you know，whether I was a cop or not，
当你破产的时候，你知道，无论我是不是警察
you know，if there was anything I could've done，
如果有什么事我做得到的
I would've done it，and I just want you to know that.
我就会去做，我只想你知道
Is that why you let that dude go in L.A.？
所以你在洛杉矶的时候就放了那家伙？
Yeah。I think that had a lot to do with it.
是的 我认为解决问题有多种方式
When I got busted，it wasn't your fault.
当我倒闭的时候，那并不是你的错
It was all on me，Mr。Roman pearce
全都怪我，罗马皮斯…
wild-and-out crazy，man.
生性野蛮的狂人
No one can tell me nothin;
谁的话我都不听
- Ridin' solo。- Yeah，well，not anymore.
- 独来独往 - 是，嗯，以后再也不是了
Not anymore，bro.
再也不是了，兄弟
I got Verone's Navigator leavin' the residence.
维安车离开了他的住所
Copy。Sir，we've got Verone on the move to the airstrip.
收到 长官，我们收到维安正去飞机跑道
Good。Let's get a bird in the air。Tell him to keep his distance.
好 我们突袭他 告诉他别靠太近
- Good and tight。Ready to go。- Channel two。Channel two.
- 装备好 准备出发 - 频道二 频道二
- You're all set。- Thanks.
- 都准备好 - 谢谢
- All set？- Yep。Let's do it.
- 准备好了？- 是的 出发吧
Report.
报告
What's goin'on out there？
外面情况怎么样？
- Team one checking in。- Team two checking in.
- 1小队准备好了 - 2小队准备好了
- Team three checking in。- Team four。All clear here too.
- 3小队准备好了 - 4小队 全部到位
Team five checkin' in.
5小队准备好了
This is team six。All clear.
6小队 就位
- Here we go。- Yeah，so you know what to do.
- 出发 - 是，你知道怎么做啦
Just stay cool，keep focused.
保持冷静，集中精神
Remember，the airstrip's on Nallwood Avenue.
记住，飞机跑道在诺木大街
It's the third exit after the bridge.
过桥后第三个出口
- Got it。- So what up，man？You ready for this？
- 明白 - 还好吗？伙计，准备好了吗？
Come on，man。Guns，murderers and crooked cops？
别这样 枪支，杀人犯，坏警察？
I was made for this，brah.
我都不怕
Come on.
过来
[Spanish]
[西班牙语]
I got activity at Verone's trailer property.
维安 的拖车里面有情况
Do not move an inch until I tell you to.
在我下命令之前不要轻举妄动
[Spanish]
[西班牙语]
Load up.
放上车去
All units，move on the trailer property right now。Move！
全部单位注意，马上到拖车那 行动！
Shit！Local p.D。is moving in on our guys.
妈的！当地警察去我们的人那里了
- Three bags in one car，huh？- Guess so.
- 3包都在同一个车？哼？- 猜猜会怎样
Cops.
警察
- I'm not goin' back to jail。- Where you goin'，man？Let's go！Let's go！
- 我不想再回到监狱 - 你去哪伙计！快走，走
[Spanish] What is he doin'？
[西班牙语] 他在干什么？
Okay，now let's get the chopper over them。I want eyes right on top.
好，现在让直升机跟着他们 就在他们头顶上
You got it。Lima 25，follow G.P.S.
好的 L25，跟踪 GPS
You know what you're doin'，man？
你知道你在干什么吗？
Stay with me，Rome。Stay with me。Come on，man.
跟着我，罗 跟着我 快
I've got 'em heading south on I-95.
他们在I-95街上正朝南面走
Bring in the aerial E.S.D.'s.
空中监控报道
Oh，shit！
噢，妈的！
- They're catching up，man！- Shut up，man！
- 他们追上来了！- 闭嘴！
- Yeah，nice drivin'，Rome。Nice drivin'。- I gotcha，Brian.
- 耶，好车技，罗 好车技 - 我赶上你了，布赖恩
Check it out，man！
你瞧，伙计！
What was that？
那是什么？
Oh，shit.
噢，妈的
- Come on，man。Take the wheel。- No。I can't drive.
- 来，扶住方向盘 - 不 我不会开
- Just hold the wheel！- I can't drive！
- 扶住方向盘就行！- 我不会！
Hold it right there！Just hold it steady，just like that.
扶住这里！只需稳住它，就这样
What are you doin'，man？
你在干什么？
Que pasa？
[西班牙语]
[Spanish]
Whoo！Yeah，man！
喔！耶！
Hold.
稳住
Bilkins，the bird's in place.
比尔金斯，小鸟到了
Yeah。We got Verone's Navigator.
耶 我们看到维安的车了
All right。Money's in transit。Sit tight.
好 钱还在路上 潜伏好
You're a good driver，man.
你是个好车手，伙计
Thanks，bro.
谢谢，兄弟
We've got the area blocked ahead。They've got nowhere to go.
我们前面的路都封锁了 他们没地方逃了
Oh！What was that？
哦！那是什么？
I've got a visual。Video should be coming through.
我看到了 视频马上就来
We got it。Looks good.
我们看到了 看起来很好
Where are they going？
他们要去哪？
Oh，shit！
哦，妈的！
All right，Miami's finest，let's see what you got.
好，迈阿密警察，看你们追不追得上
Come on。Stay with me，boys.
快 跟我来，伙计
- Hey，man。Everyone's here。Time for the show。- Let's give it to 'em.
- 嗨，伙计 人都到了 好戏该上演了 - 让他们瞧瞧吧
All right。Let the party begin。Let's go.
好 派对开始吧 走
This is unit 2599。We have the suspects surrounded.
这里是 2599 单位 我们包围嫌疑犯了
[Spanish]
[西班牙语]
Holy shit！
哦天啊！
It's a scramble，baby。A big one！
真混乱，宝贝 真大场面！
Yeah！Let's do this！
耶！来吧！
Check this out！
快瞧！
We're not tracking them on video.
我们在视频上追逐不到他们
Must have lost them in the scramble.
混乱中丢失了
Y'all，let's break.
我们走吧
Yeah！
耶！
[Spanish]
[西班牙语]
All right。We got 'em going west on Beach.
好 我们发现他们了，去住西海滩
Roger that。I've got 'em.
收到 我会跟上的
Customs has a fix on two cars going west on Beach.
海关盯住两辆往西去海滩的车
- Roger。Follow those cars。- Roger that.
- 收到 跟住它 - 收到
Shit。They're cornered.
妈的 他们被逼到无路可走了
keep your hands where I can see 'em.！
把你们的手放到我们能看到的地方！
- put your hands up.！- Whoa。Fellas，fellas.
- 举起手！- 喔 伙计
I know my tags are out of date，but，damn！
我知道我的车牌过期了，但是，该死的！
What the hell？Where are they？
什么回事？他们哪去了？
Man.！How about them apples，man？
这场秀怎么样？
Yeah！That's some drivin' for your ass，baby！Ain't that some drivin' for your ass？
耶！你的司机怎么样，宝贝！是不是很爽啊？
- Good job，man。- Whatever，man.
- 干得好，伙计 - 算不了什么
You supposed to be a stone-face killer.
你就像是个石脸杀手
You over there grabbin' your seat belt.
你刚才稳抓安全带的时候
Hey，Tej。Thanks a lot。You're the clutch。I owe you one，big time.
嘿，泰 非常感谢 你太棒了 我欠你个大人情
Yeah，Brian，you really do owe me，man.
是的，布赖恩，你确实欠我个人情
You really do Us。Suki says you owe us，a'ight？
你确实欠…我们 舒琪说你欠我们，对不？
- Yo，Rome。You there，man？Come in。- What's up，man？
- 唷，罗 你听到吗？回话 - 怎么啦，伙计？
It looks like we got just one more trick left，huh？
我们只剩下最后一个计划了，哼？
My pleasure，buddy。Let's do it，baby.
乐意奉陪，兄弟 干吧
- Hey。We should grab Verone while we still can。- No。Not yet.
- 嗨 要乘我们还有能力的时候抓了 维安 - 不 还不行
What？You lost 'em？
什么？你们跟失了他们？
Shit！Those little pricks are running.
妈的！那些混蛋逃了
- It's your call。What do you want to do？- We're gonna take him down.
- 听你的 我们现在怎么办？- 我们把他拿下
He is not leaving here.
他不能离开这里
Enjoyin' the ride？Man，it's a fast car，huh？
坐得过瘾吗？很快是吧？
Man，it's a classic.
技术是一流的
Old school。American muscle.
守旧派 美国肌肉
Man，this car can do all kinda things，man.
伙计，这车能做任何的事
Wanna see？
想见识一下吗？
Check this out right here，homey.
把这松开
- Yo！What are you doin'，man？- Shut up！
- 唷！你想干什么？- 闭嘴！
[Spanish]
[西班牙语]
It worked.！I love this button.！
果然有效！我喜欢这个按钮！
Stay on your toes，puto！
乖乖呆在那里吧！
Mr。O'Conner，it worked，baby.
欧康纳，搞定了，宝贝
Blow and go。I'm all clear.
送他出去了 我这搞掂了
- Meet me at the point。Hurry up，man。It's on，baby。- All right。Ten-four，man.
- 我们在那里见 快点，伙计 - 好 伙计
Are you ready？Let's go！
准备好了吗？行动！
I got this side.！
我抄这边！
Raise your hands！Raise your hands！Raise your hands！
举起手来！
Get down！Get down！Get down！
爬下！
Clear.！We're clear.！
清场！我们清场了！
Back it up.！
退后！
- It's not Verone and Fuentes。- What do you mean？
- 维安 和 芳特斯不在这 - 你说什么？
Then where the hell are they？
那他们哪去了？
Get off at Tarpon point.
在前面大海鲢处下高速
Tarpon point？There's There's no airstrip at Tarpon point.
大海鲢？那不是…去飞机跑道的
Who said anything about an airstrip？
谁说要去飞机跑道那的？
Brian。Brian，man，what's the holdup，brah？
布赖恩 布赖恩，怎么啦？
- Yo，Rome，there's a new plan。- What the hell？
- 罗，有新计划 - 什么？
We're meeting them at the Tarpon point exit，not the airstrip.
我们在大海鲢的高速出口碰面，不是去飞机跑道
- So what are you sayin'？- Like I said，there's a new plan.
- 你在说什么？- 新计划
Brian。Brian，hello？You there？
布赖恩 布赖恩，哈罗？你听到吗？
- Damn！- Yo！What the hell is he doin'？
- 该死的！- 他搞什么鬼？
The feds are in the wrong place。Brian's woman is on her own with Verone.
联邦人员搞错地方了 布赖恩的女人和 维安 一伙的
- So - So Brian's not comin'.
- 那… - 布赖恩 不会来这了
- It's all right。Let him out。- Get out.
- 好 让他出来 - 出来
pop the trunk。[Spanish]
把箱子拿出来 [西班牙语]
Hurry up.
快点
- Where's the rest of it？- The other car.
- 其他的呢？- 另外一辆车
- Another car。Where's the other car？- On it's way.
- 另外一辆车 另外一辆车在哪？- 在路上
- On the way，huh？- Yeah。Here's your money.
- 在路上，是吗？- 是 这是你的钱
So you know nothing about the agents that stormed my jet？
你对那些监视我的飞机的探员一无所知？
The funny thing is that I only told one person about the airstrip.
有趣的是我只告诉 过一个人关于飞机跑道的事
Hmm.
嗯
Customs agents sure are gettin' pretty，aren't they？
海关人员越来越厉害了，是不？
Put her on the boat.
带她上船
- Let's go。- Get on the boat.
- 走 - 上船
- Hide the cars and get rid of him。- Back in the car.
- 藏好车，干了他 - 回车里去
End of the road.
到尽头了
You know，I like you，but I still gotta kill you.
你知道，我喜欢你，但我还是要杀了你
It's my job.
这是我的工作
What's that？
那是什么？
- What's that？- It's Barstow，baby！It's about to get ugly！
- 那是什么？- 快动手，宝贝！太糟糕了！
Let's go。Let's go.
走 走
Get your Oh，shit！
拿开你的…哦，妈的！
Come on.
来
You had me.
你差点骗了我
You slipped.
你犯错了
Eleven and a half months，and you slipped once.
11个半月里面你就犯了这一次错
put her downstairs.
带她下去
I'll see you in a second.
迟点见
- I thought you was dead，man。- Yeah。Me too。Thanks for saving my ass，bro.
- 我以为你死了 - 我也以为我死定了 谢谢你救了我
- What are you doin'，Brian？- I don't know，
- 你在干什么，布赖恩？- 我不知道
but if Verone sees a helicopter or Customs boat，she's dead.
但如果 维安 遇到海关的 直升飞机或者船，她救死定了
Boat。Car.
艇 车
Boat You're not gonna do what I think you're gonna do？
艇… 你不会想我想象的那样干吧？
- Yeah，I think so。You got my back，bro？- Yeah.
- 是，我想是 你支持我吗？- 是
- put on a seat belt。- Show 'em some real Dukes of Hazzard shit.
- 系好安全带 - 给他们点真颜色看看
We're gonna do this big。Hold on，Rome。Hold on.
让我们大干一场吧 坐稳 罗 坐稳
Oh.！Brian，you crazy，man.！What the hell you doin'？
哦！布赖恩，你疯了吗！你要干什么？
Brian，what the hell you doin'？
布赖恩，你要干什么？
Whoa！
噢！
Shit！
妈的！
My arm。I think I broke my arm，man.
我的手臂 我想我的手臂断了
Get the gun.
拿住枪
It's over，Carter.
结束了，卡特
- You okay？- Yeah.
- 你还好吗？- 是
I'm great.
我很好
We got 'em，man。We got 'em.
我们赢了，我们赢了
Let's get outta here.
我们出去吧
Go！Go！
走！走！
That ought to do it.
应该这样
So，there were three bags total，huh？The three from the boat.
总共有三袋，哼？船上搜出三袋钱
So we good，right？My record's clean？
所以我们没事了，是吗？我们的档案会清了对吗？
You held up your end。Your records are clean.
你们坚持到了最后 你的案底已经撤销了
So maybe there was six bags.
也许应该是6袋
I guess we can call it even.
我想我们扯平了
- Agent Dunn。- Sir.
- 当长官 - 在
We found some more evidence.
我们找到更多的证据
Come on。Let's take it to the truck.
来 拿上货车去
Don't drop the soap，big homey.
进去后别那么拽
I hope you know that when he gets out，he's gonna kill your ass.
我希望你知道，他出来以后一定会杀了你
He ain't gettin' out.
他不会再出来了
- I'll see you soon。- You think he gonna get out？
- 我们很快又见面的 - 你认为他会出来？
He'll be out.
他会出来的
No，for real。You think he gettin' out，though？
不，说真的，他会出来？
We took care of your decoys。They're free and clear.
我们处理了你们的档案 你们自由和洗清罪名了
There's a sedan out on the road for you.
外面的车是送你的
- Try to bring it back in one piece。- Yeah.
- 去修好他吧 - 好
- Thanks a lot，Bilkins。You're all right。- Thanks.
- 谢谢，比尔金斯 你真好人 - 不客气
- Thanks for lookin' out，man。- All right.
- 谢谢你照顾 - 还好
- So you trust me now？- You a'ight.
- 现在信任我了吗？- 你还好
Sorry。Nice working with you，O'Conner.
对不起 干得太棒了，欧康纳
Same here.
彼此彼此
Mm。I'm-a have to stay out here in Miami，man.
嗯 我必须离开这里
Keep you out of trouble，brah.
以免你惹上麻烦，兄弟
You know what I'm talkin' about.
你知道我在说什么吗
So you gonna kick it in Miami，bro？
那你要离开迈阿密吗？
Oh，man，I love Miami.
我爱迈阿密
Miami's off the hook.
我迷上迈阿密了
- Open a garage together。- A garage？
- 一起开间汽车修理厂怎么样 - 修理厂？
How we gonna do that，brah？
怎么开？
Pockets ain't empty，cuz.
口袋不是空的，笨蛋
And we ain't hungry no more either，brah.
我们也不会再挨饿了，兄弟